[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Chinese Zodiac, what is the last year in the twelve-year cycle?", "correct_answer": "the year of the boar", "incorrect_answers": ["the year of the ox", "the year of the snake", "the year of the tiger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which member of the Balboa household was celebrating a birthday at the beginning of the movie Rocky IV?", "correct_answer": "Paulie", "incorrect_answers": ["Adrian Balboa", "Rocky Senior", "Rocky Junior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following are usually part of every restaurant table setting?", "correct_answer": "Salt and pepper", "incorrect_answers": ["Bread and butter", "Ketchup and mustard", "Olive oil and vinegar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What dish is traditionally served for breakfast in Cambodia, Thailand and Vietnam?", "correct_answer": "Soup", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish", "Pork chops", "Fried potatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "President George W. Bush was inaugurated on January 20, 2000.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The setting of The City of God is in this cyti.", "correct_answer": "Rio de Janeiro", "incorrect_answers": ["Madrid", "Barcelona", "Caracas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elena Andrionovna was born to Andrian Nikolayev and Valentina Tereshkova. Which statement is true about her?", "correct_answer": "Both her parents had been in outer space.", "incorrect_answers": ["She was the first child born after the demise of the USSR.", "She was the first child born by a surrogate mother.", "She was the first child born in the offices of the KGB."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the oldest known ink come from?", "correct_answer": "China and India", "incorrect_answers": ["India and Turkey", "England and China", "France and Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these species of geckos is able to glide in the air after jumping or falling from a tree?", "correct_answer": "Ptychozoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Gold dust day gecko", "Uroplatus fimbriatus", "Leopard gecko"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term facultative carnivore mean?", "correct_answer": "A carnivore that also consumes plant food.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is a synonym for scavenger.", "Animal that has all characteristics of carnivores but is a herbivore.", "It is a synonym for omnivore."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What order of trilobite was the only one to survive the Devonian mass extinction?", "correct_answer": "Proetida", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Phacopida", "Lichida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Mia have a crush on in the movie The Princess Diaries?", "correct_answer": "Josh", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe", "Michael", "Bobby Bad"]}]